{
    "subject": "resource/Gustave_Choquet",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/France",
    "human_readable": "Gustave Choquet is from France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9855403304100037,
            "question": "Is France the origin of Gustave Choquet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9831367135047913,
            "question": "Is Gustave Choquet French?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8576825857162476,
            "question": "Where is Gustave Choquet from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7811720371246338,
            "question": "From which nation hails Gustave Choquet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7588620185852051,
            "question": "Where was Gustave Choquet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7066839337348938,
            "question": "What country is associated with Gustave Choquet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6957306265830994,
            "question": "In what country did Gustave Choquet reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6865453720092773,
            "question": "What is Gustave Choquet's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750467419624329,
            "question": "To which country does Gustave Choquet belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.589259922504425,
            "question": "Can you tell me Gustave Choquet's nationality?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gustave Choquet is from France.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6011_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Gustave Choquet belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6011_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Gustave Choquet's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6011_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country did Gustave Choquet reside?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6011_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6011_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the documents, I found that:\n\n* Gustave Choquet's birthplace and nationality are mentioned multiple times throughout the documents. According to the information, he was born in different locations (Solesmes, Nord; Paris; Pont-l'\u00c9v\u00eaque) on various dates (1 March 1915; 28 October 1923; 17 July 1985), but his country of origin is consistently stated as France.\n* The documents also mention that Gustave Choquet was a French mathematician and artist, which reinforces the idea that he is from France.\n\nTherefore, based on this analysis, I can confidently conclude that:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the fact that multiple documents mention Gustave Choquet being French, such as \"Gustave Choquet (French: [\u0283\u0254k\u025b]; 1 March 1915 \u2013 14 November 2006) was a French mathematician.\" and \"Gustave Choquet was born on February 1, 1923 in France.\" Therefore, the statement that Gustave Choquet is from France is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}